Justin Hohing

60 Harding Ave Runnemede, NJ 08078 Phone Number: 609-313-7847 probalicous13@gmail.com

Summary

ColdFusion Software Developer/DBA experienced in web design and functionality, troubleshooting, proficient in SQL, and managing and creating tables in a relational database environment. Pursuing growth and knowledge in areas of database management and web applications development using languages such as ColdFusion, ASP.NET, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap and CSS.

Experience

Inspira Health Network - Bridgeton, NJ

Programmer – March 2018 – present

- Manage reports using CCL (Cerner Command Language) for doctors and nurses
- Manage management planning tool (Blueprint)
- Upload data through a data upload tool into a system that normalizes the data (HIDUU)
- Troubleshooting user issues and report issues
- Experience with HTML, CSS, Typescript, C#, SQL, CCL
- Tools used: Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Microsoft SQL Server Management Studio
- Experienced in Cerner Works Tools: Discern Visual Developer, Discern Admin, PowerInsight, PowerChart, Discern Analytics 2.0, Discern Reporting Portal.

Comtekh Inc. - Berlin N.J

ColdFusion Developer/DBA - September 2015 – December 2017

- Web applications development and implementation
- Experienced in HTML, Visual Basic, ColdFusion, C++, ASP.NET
- Data Analytics/Integrity/Normalization
- Design dynamic websites and tools utilizing JQuery, Javascript, Bootstrap and CSS
- Troubleshooting
- Worked in TEMS & Metrics
- Tools used: Notepad++, Microsoft SQL Server 2012, GitHub, Visual Studio

Comtekh Inc. - Berlin NJ

HelpDesk - September 2012 - September 2015 (3 years 1 month)

- -Worked tickets in multiple platforms (Service Now, CIBOR)
- Data Comm and Wide Area Networking (MPLS,ISP, P2P)
- Global Voice Operations Support
- Personal Telecom Services
- On call support/Customer service for network outages & personal services

Panera Bread - Mt. Laurel, NJ

Associate – November 2011 - March 2012 (5 months)

Worked food line and as a bus boy

Education

Rutgers Coding Bootcamp - Online through bootcampspot.com

Online programming bootcamp to become full stack web developer Covers HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, MongoDB, MySQL, and GitHub December 2020 – May 2021

Camden County College - Blackwood, NJ

Associates, Management Information Systems, General, 2016 - 2017

Eastern Regional High School - Voorhees, NJ

2008 - 2012

Activities and Societies: Volleyball

Hobbies

- Volleyball - Drumming/Music - CrossFit/Exercising - Traveling